You are here » [Home](https://www.seymourlerhn.com/) » Privacy Policy

[

](https://www.seymourlerhn.com/ "Seymour & Lerhn")

The Small Print…
----------------

### Seymour & Lerhn Privacy Policy | May 2018

#### **Privacy Policy – Issue April 2021**

**Introduction**

_Seymour & Lerhn is a service provider of immersive learning tools including 360, VR, AR and interactive digital experiences for schools, museums, heritage, and outreach._

 _This Privacy Policy outlines our use of Personal Information in line with the_ **Data Protection Act 2018** _and_ **General Data** **Protection Regulation (GDPR)**.

_This page is used to inform visitors regarding our policies with the collection, use, and disclosure of Personal Information for website visitors and platform users._

**General**

If you choose to use our Service, then you agree to the collection and use of information in relation to this policy. The Personal Information that we collect is used for providing and improving the Service. We will not use or share your information with anyone except as described in this Privacy Policy.

The terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meanings as in our Terms and Conditions, which is accessible at [www.seymourlerhn.com/terms-and-conditions](http://www.seymourlerhn.com/terms-and-conditions)

#### **Information Collection and Use**

**Website**

For a better experience while using our Service we may require certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

The online platform may use third party services to track visitor usage of the site to enhance and improve the visitor experience. 

When you visit our site we store the website from which you visited us from, the parts of our site you visit, the date and duration of your visit, and information from the device (device type, operating system, screen resolution, language, country you are located in, and web browser type) you used during your visit. We only capture and store a truncated version of your IP address. It is captured and stored in an anonymised format by suppressing the last octet so your full IP address never reaches our servers and we never have access to it.

We process this usage data to facilitate your access to our services (e.g. to adjust our services to the device you are using), and to recognise and stop any misuse. We also process usage data in an anonymised form for statistical purposes and to improve our site.

The websites may also contain other tracking technologies such as “web beacons” or “pixels.” These are typically small transparent images that provide us with statistics, for similar purposes as cookies. They are often used in conjunction with cookies, though they are not stored on your computer in the same way. As a result, if you disable cookies, web beacons may still load, but their functionality will be restricted. 

We operate our ads program in partnership with third party vendors. As part of the operation of our ads program, we use cookies to collect certain information. Advertising cookies enable us and our partners to serve ads and to personalise those ads based on information like visits to our sites and other sites on the Internet.

You can manage your cookie preferences at any time.

**Online Purchases**

By making a purchase on seymourlerhn.com, you agree to the use of your data in line with this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions of Use.

In order to make a purchase, you will be required to supply certain personal information (Name, Billing Address, Payment Details, Email Address) to process the transaction. This information is securely processed and stored through our payment gateway providers; Woocommerce and Stripe. Data we hold is only accessible to key personnel for the purposes of processing your transaction and we do not have access to payment card details.

If you make a purchase through the online store, you will be served third-party cookies to enable the sales process to function correctly. These cookies are only used for core functionality and will not track your activity or serve targeted advertising once you have left the website.

You can find out more about third-party data policies here:

**User Accounts**

By creating an account, you agree to the use of your data in line with this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions of Use.

In order to register an account, you will be required to supply certain personal information. This information is securely stored within the website and is only accessible to key personnel for the purposes of managing your account.

If you create an account, you will be served third-party cookies to enable access to otherwise restricted parts of the website. These cookies are only used for core functionality and will not track your activity or serve targeted advertising once you have left the website.

You can find out more about these cookies here:

**Online Education Platform**

By using the [Online Education Platform](https://www.seymourlerhn.com/platform/) you agree to the use of your data in line with this Privacy Policy and the Terms & Conditions of Use.

In order to register an account, you will be required to supply certain personal information. This information is securely stored within the website and is only accessible to key personnel for the purposes of managing your account.

Accounts for children are set up by the account manager and/or teacher accounts and does not require personal information. The person creating these accounts should ensure that the username does not include personal information about children under the age of 16; for example real names, birthdays, student numbers, email addresses or any other unique data which could be used to identify a child or when could identify a child when combined with other data supplied.

You will also be served a cookie which is linked to your subscription and account and will allow access to otherwise restricted areas of the site. This is an essential cookie which is used for core functionality and will not track your activity or serve targeted advertising once you have left the website.

Although the platform does not use analytics tracking or third-party cookies for analytics or tracking purposes, certain embedded elements may serve third-party cookies which we have no control over.

We strongly recommend reviewing the privacy policies of these third parties and understanding how your data is managed before using these services within the platform:

**AR**

Some of our apps and online content use AR (Augmented Reality). Content using AR will include ‘AR’ in the name. To enable this to work, the application must have access to the camera. The camera is only used during active use. No data or images from the camera are collected or stored by Seymour & Lerhn or any other third party. 

**Apps**

For a better experience, while using our Service, we may require you to provide us with certain personally identifiable information. The information that we request will be retained by us and used as described in this privacy policy.

Seymour & Lerhn Apps use third party services that may collect information used to identify you.

Link to privacy policy of third party service providers used by the app

**Cookies**

Seymour & Lerhn uses cookies to provide secure subscription access to the subscription section of the website. Cookies are small data files transferred onto computers or devices by sites for record-keeping purposes and to enhance functionality on our site.

These cookies will only be used to check for a valid subscription to allow access to restricted or paid areas of the site. Cookies are stored on your individual device and you have full control over their use. You may deactivate or restrict the transmission of cookies by changing the settings of your web browser. Cookies that are already stored may be deleted at any time. Should you visit Seymour & Lerhn’s site with cookies deactivated, you may not be able to use all of the functions on our site to the full extent.

**Security**

We value your trust in providing us your Personal Information, and we are striving to use all commercially acceptable means of protecting it. But remember that no method of transmission over the internet, or method of electronic storage is 100% secure and reliable, and we cannot guarantee its absolute security.

**Links to Other Sites**

This Service may contain links to other sites. If you click on a third-party link, you will be directed to that site. Note that these external sites are not operated by us. Therefore, we strongly advise you to review the Privacy Policy of these websites. We have no control over and assume no responsibility for the content, privacy policies, or practices of any third-party sites or services.

**Children’s Privacy and Safeguarding**

This Policy and Services do not apply anyone under the age of 16. We do not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under 16. In the case we discover that the Personal Information of a child under 16 has been provided, we immediately delete this from our servers. If you are a parent or guardian and you are aware that your child has provided us with personal information or information has been supplied on their behalf, please contact us.

**Provisions to comply with the General Data Protection Regulation**

1. UK Data Protection Law will change on 25 May 2018 when the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679) takes effect.
2. Either you and/or your affiliates, including subsidiaries and holding companies, have a sub-contract, supply agreement, consultancy agreement or other contractual agreement in place with a company within the Oasis Studio Group (Oasis Urban Estates Ltd).
3. The provisions of this Addendum will come into force between you and the Oasis Studio Group (Oasis Urban Estates Ltd), from 25 May 2018, to coincide with the taking effect of the GDPR.

**Oasis Urban Estates Ltd:** whose registered office is at Unit 4, Chatsworth Technology Park, Dunston Road, Chesterfield, S41 8XA and its subsidiaries from time to time.

**Contract:** the sub-contract, supply agreement, consultancy agreement or other contractual agreement in place between you and the Oasis Studio Group.

**Data Controller, Data Processor, Data Subject, Personal Data:** have the meanings ascribed to them in the GDPR.

**Data Protection Legislation:** the UK Data Protection Legislation and (for so long as and to the extent that the law of the European Union has legal effect in the UK) the GDPR and any other directly applicable European Union regulation relating to privacy.

**GDPR:** the EU General Data Protection Regulation ((EU) 2016/679)

**UK Data Protection Legislation:** any data protection legislation from time to time in force in the UK including the Data Protection Act 1998 or 2018 or any successor legislation.

**Data Protection Obligations**

1. Both parties will comply with all applicable requirements of the Data Protection Legislation. This clause is in addition to, and does not relieve, remove or replace, a party’s obligations under the Data Protection Legislation.
2. Where we make available Personal Data to you in relation to the performance of the Contract:

* * the parties acknowledge that for the purposes of the Data Protection Legislation, the Relevant Oasis Studio Company is the Data Controller and you are the Data Processor.
    * the Relevant Oasis Studio Company will ensure that it has all necessary appropriate consents and notices in place to enable lawful transfer of Personal Data to you for the duration and purposes of the Contract.

3. Where you make available Personal Data to us in relation to the performance of the Contract:

* * the parties acknowledge that for the purposes of the Data Protection Legislation, you are the Data Controller and the Relevant Oasis Studio Company is the Data Processor.
    * you will ensure that you have all necessary appropriate consents and notices in place to enable lawful transfer of Personal Data to us for the duration and purposes of the Contract.

4. In relation to any Personal Data processed in connection with the performance by either party of its obligations under the Contract, the parties confirm that:

* * Personal Data shall only be processed on the written instructions of the Data Controller unless the Data Processor is required by Data Protection Legislation to otherwise process that Personal Data;
    * they will ensure that they have in place appropriate technical and organisational measures to protect against unauthorised or unlawful processing of Personal Data and against accidental loss or destruction of, or damage to, Personal Data, appropriate to the harm that might result from the unauthorised or unlawful processing or accidental loss, destruction or damage and the nature of the data to be protected, having regard to the state of technological development and the cost of implementing any measures (those measures may include, where appropriate, pseudonymising and encrypting Personal Data, ensuring confidentiality, integrity, availability and resilience of its systems and services, ensuring that availability of and access to Personal Data can be restored in a timely manner after an incident, and regularly assessing and evaluating the effectiveness of the technical and organisational measures adopted by it);
    * they will ensure that all personnel who have access to and/or process Personal Data are obliged to keep the Personal Data confidential;
    * they will not transfer any Personal Data outside of the European Economic Area unless the prior written consent of the other party has been obtained (which consent may include conditions relating to the transfer of that Personal Data);
    * they will assist the other party in responding to any request from a Data Subject and in ensuring compliance with its obligations under the Data Protection Legislation with respect to security, breach notifications, impact assessments and consultations with supervisory authorities or regulators;
    * they will notify the other party without undue delay on becoming aware of a Personal Data breach;
    * they will, at the written direction of the other party, delete or return Personal Data and copies thereof to the other party on termination of the agreement unless required by Data Protection Legislation to store the Personal Data;

**Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Thus, you are advised to review this page periodically for any changes. We will notify you of any changes by posting the new Privacy Policy on this page. These changes are effective immediately after they are posted on this page.

**Contact Us**

If you have any questions or suggestions about our Privacy Policy, do not hesitate to contact us at [hello@seymourlerhn.com](mailto:hello@seymourlerhn.com).

##### Mmm... Cookies!

Our site uses cookies, by clicking okay you agree to our [privacy policy](https://www.seymourlerhn.com/privacy-policy/).  

PreferencesOkay!

Manage consent

Close

#### Privacy Overview

This website uses cookies to improve your experience while you navigate through the website. Out of these, the cookies that are categorized as necessary are stored on your browser as they are essential for the working of basic functionalities of the website. We also use third-party cookies that help us analyze and understand how you use this website. These cookies will be stored in your browser only with your consent. You also have the option to opt-out of these cookies. But opting out of some of these cookies may affect your browsing experience.

Necessary

 Necessary

Always Enabled

Necessary cookies are absolutely essential for the website to function properly. These cookies ensure basic functionalities and security features of the website, anonymously.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_\_stripe\_mid | 1 year | This cookie is set by Stripe payment gateway. This cookie is used to enable payment on the website without storing any payment information on a server. |
| \_\_stripe\_sid | 30 minutes | This cookie is set by Stripe payment gateway. This cookie is used to enable payment on the website without storing any payment information on a server. |
| \_GRECAPTCHA | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Google. In addition to certain standard Google cookies, reCAPTCHA sets a necessary cookie (\_GRECAPTCHA) when executed for the purpose of providing its risk analysis. |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-analytics | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Analytics". |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-functional | 11 months | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Functional". |
| cookielawinfo-checbox-others | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Other. |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-advertisement | 1 year | The cookie is set by GDPR cookie consent to record the user consent for the cookies in the category "Advertisement". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-necessary | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookies is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Necessary". |
| cookielawinfo-checkbox-performance | 11 months | This cookie is set by GDPR Cookie Consent plugin. The cookie is used to store the user consent for the cookies in the category "Performance". |
| viewed\_cookie\_policy | 11 months | The cookie is set by the GDPR Cookie Consent plugin and is used to store whether or not user has consented to the use of cookies. It does not store any personal data. |

Functional

 Functional

Functional cookies help to perform certain functionalities like sharing the content of the website on social media platforms, collect feedbacks, and other third-party features.

Performance

 Performance

Performance cookies are used to understand and analyze the key performance indexes of the website which helps in delivering a better user experience for the visitors.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| YSC | session | This cookie is set by YouTube and is used to track the views of embedded videos. |

Analytics

 Analytics

Analytical cookies are used to understand how visitors interact with the website. These cookies help provide information on metrics the number of visitors, bounce rate, traffic source, etc.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_ga | 2 years | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to calculate visitor, session, campaign data and keep track of site usage for the site's analytics report. The cookies store information anonymously and assign a randomly generated number to identify unique visitors. |
| \_ga\_V4VS8XZGZV | 2 years | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. |
| \_gat\_gtag\_UA\_117859430\_1 | 1 minute | Google uses this cookie to distinguish users. |
| \_gid | 1 day | This cookie is installed by Google Analytics. The cookie is used to store information of how visitors use a website and helps in creating an analytics report of how the website is doing. The data collected including the number visitors, the source where they have come from, and the pages visted in an anonymous form. |
| \_hjAbsoluteSessionInProgress | 30 minutes | Hotjar helps us to improve the website based on user interaction. This cookie is used to detect the first pageview session of a user. This is a True/False flag set by the cookie. |
| \_hjFirstSeen | 30 minutes | Hotjar helps us to improve the website based on user interaction. This is set by Hotjar to identify a new user’s first session. It stores a true/false value, indicating whether this was the first time Hotjar saw this user. It is used by Recording filters to identify new user sessions. |
| \_hjid | 1 year | This cookie is set by Hotjar. Hotjar helps us to improve the website based on user interaction. This cookie is set when the customer first lands on a page with the Hotjar script. It is used to persist the random user ID, unique to that site on the browser. This ensures that behavior in subsequent visits to the same site will be attributed to the same user ID. |
| \_hjIncludedInPageviewSample | 2 minutes | Hotjar helps us to improve the website based on user interaction. This cookie is set to let Hotjar know whether that user is included in the data sampling defined by the site's pageview limit. |
| \_hjTLDTest | session | When the Hotjar script executes we try to determine the most generic cookie path we should use, instead of the page hostname. This is done so that cookies can be shared across subdomains (where applicable). To determine this, we try to store the \_hjTLDTest cookie for different URL substring alternatives until it fails. After this check, the cookie is removed. |

Advertisement

 Advertisement

Advertisement cookies are used to provide visitors with relevant ads and marketing campaigns. These cookies track visitors across websites and collect information to provide customized ads.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| \_fbp | 3 months | This cookie is set by Facebook to deliver advertisement when they are on Facebook or a digital platform powered by Facebook advertising after visiting this website. |
| fr  | 3 months | The cookie is set by Facebook to show relevant advertisments to the users and measure and improve the advertisements. The cookie also tracks the behavior of the user across the web on sites that have Facebook pixel or Facebook social plugin. |
| IDE | 1 year 24 days | Used by Google DoubleClick and stores information about how the user uses the website and any other advertisement before visiting the website. This is used to present users with ads that are relevant to them according to the user profile. |
| NID | 6 months | The NID cookie contains a unique ID Google uses to remember your preferences and other information, such as your preferred language (e.g. English), how many search results you wish to have shown per page (e.g. 10 or 20), and whether or not you wish to have Google’s SafeSearch filter turned on. |
| test\_cookie | 15 minutes | This cookie is set by doubleclick.net. The purpose of the cookie is to determine if the user's browser supports cookies. |
| VISITOR\_INFO1\_LIVE | 5 months 27 days | This cookie is set by Youtube. Used to track the information of the embedded YouTube videos on a website. |

Others

 Others

Other uncategorized cookies are those that are being analyzed and have not been classified into a category as yet.

| Cookie | Duration | Description |
| --- | --- | --- |
| CONSENT | 16 years 7 months 25 days 15 hours 9 minutes | No description |
| lfuuid | 9 years 8 months 25 days 15 hours 9 minutes | User tracking for enhanced performance |
| m   | 2 years | No description |
| S   | 1 hour | No description |
| wp\_woocommerce\_session\_61e484ba3b3baff16dfbc76f84de5edb | 2 days | No description |
| yt-remote-connected-devices | never | Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video |
| yt-remote-device-id | never | Stores the user's video player preferences using embedded YouTube video |

SAVE & ACCEPT

Powered by [

](https://www.cookieyes.com/)
